{
    "id": "29e0ae58fc8241339888eaa279599b51",
    "title": "Until, Before, And After",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He won’t marry ................. he gets a job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "before",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1d873fbc03824ef980f72055ec2fa29f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t open the window .................. the rain stops.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "after",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e80028e74fe541e2b08193f6224cbf7f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will wait here .................. you finish your work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "before",
                "after"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fb96779c192c462aaf18ce3997c51bf1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t go ..................... I tell you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "after",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f47164efa0864db59842b08012f8a4a9"
        },
        {
            "question": "We will have to live in this house ................... we find a better one.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "before",
                "after",
                "until"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f49af0e115d6493e85ab00b07bf92ba1"
        },
        {
            "question": "He had locked the door ................. he went out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "before",
                "after",
                "until"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "afef9fa866bd4e6a8cb44b218d456da4"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must wash your hands ..................... you eat anything.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "before",
                "until",
                "after"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6faf6f3d73df480292b93db0a9ecacfe"
        },
        {
            "question": "He will finish his work ............... he goes home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "before",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0fbad886e8894ed898a54a07d4ab00ad"
        },
        {
            "question": "He had counted the coins ..................... he put them in the box.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "before",
                "after"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2f7cc8f113a44f1c8b179f0867231965"
        },
        {
            "question": "He went out to play ....................... he did his homework.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "after",
                "until",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "440c19a6e7594b51a345727aad520c6f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I put on my clothes ........................ I had washed myself.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "before",
                "until",
                "after"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "82bc15a3b2f64ff393990215a2b41e23"
        },
        {
            "question": "We reached the station ten minutes ....................... the train left.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "after",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d6568dbbea9145e8b4c09b6129abfd67"
        }
    ]
}